Mallesh Madapathi

Montreal, Quebec, Canada



malleshmadapathi@outlook.com



+14388214434



linkedin.com/in/malleshmadapathi

Summary

Master's in computer science. Passionately looking for new opportunities in

Software development, UI/UX. 3 years experience in hybrid environment

(software development and production support) and one year designing experience.

Languages: Python, Machine Learning, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, React, solid understanding of node.js.

Angular, RESTful APIs, vue.js

Databases: SQL, Solid understanding of MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB

UI/UX: Adobe CC, wireframes, graphic designing in Adobe

Understanding of tools: Git, OAuth, XCode, Android Studio, Docker, Jupyter notebook, Eclipse IDE, Active Directory, 0365, Microsoft Exchange, ServiceNow, Adobe Creative Cloud, Linux command line tools.

Experience

cgi Technical Consultant

CGI

Oct 2018 - Jul 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Client: BMO Financial Group | Programmer Analyst for various banking applications which were written in Java, Python, JavaScript, C#(.NET), C++ on Windows Platform.

Provides first level remote support to internal and external clients for a wide variety of technical Issues.



UI/UX Designer

Bishop's University

Apr 2018 - Aug 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Freelanced as UI/UX, Layout editor for student run 70yr old campus newspaper/Magazine which is bi-weekly.

Responsibilities include:

Designing, editing, formatting, planning the bi-weekly edition

Collaboration with all the various editors for implementing, designing the edition



Android Developer

Hafyaline

Jun 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Hafyalyn is an online doctor consulting application, which is used to solve patient problems, book appointments and also used to search for blood donors as well.

Education



Bishop's University

Master's degree, Computer Science

2018 - 2020